[Connecting to You]
Ever since I was a kid,
my world was a bit different
from everyone else's.
When I was a kid, I drew pictures
where everyone had  threads coming out
of their heads.
Later, I realized
it was the emotional connections
between people.
Every connection
grows into a thread.
Different feelings
grow different colored threads.
Right, the red ones are the love
connections we all understand best.
As for the blue ones,
they mean your relationship
is a bit tense.
Even though
I can see these threads,
I haven't formed
a connection with anyone.
Not a single one.
Or maybe I do have connections with others,
but I just can't see them?
I believe
there must be someone
in this world connected to me.
So I tried hard to help others,
hoping to find my own threads.
But I've also gotten myself
into a lot of trouble.
[If you don't reply,
you'll never see me again.]
People whose threads break
and who lose the will to live
are the hardest to deal with.
Stop right there!
Still trying to run?
You can't run anymore, huh?
Out of energy?
Gotcha.
Keep running, huh?
How do I distract her?
Ah, I got it.
Hey, girl.
Be careful.
I'll go take a look.
Okay.
Who are you?
I'm here to jump, too.
If you're going to jump, then jump.
Why are you taking your clothes off?
Because
I want to
kill myself naked.
Today, at this time, in this spot...
I've been planning this for a long time.
So could you
give me this spot?
Psycho.
I've also made up my mind
to kill myself today.
I want that jerk to regret what he did.
Then how about this?
You come over here first.
Let me jump first,
and then it's your turn. How about that?
Why do you get to go first?
So what if you jump naked?
I can take my clothes off, too.
Pervert! Where are you touching? Go away!
Pervert!
-Get up, you pervert! Pervert!
-Officer!
You filthy pervert,
acting like that on my turf?
-I hate perverts!
-Don't poke my butt. Don't poke my butt!
Who's poking your butt?
Now you're making false accusations, huh?
Sorry, I gave in.
[The first Thread]
[Loss Aversion:
I Didn't Like You at First]
Okay, it's alright.
-It's alright. It's alright.
-My call records are gone.
Okay, it's alright.
So you mean
you took off all your clothes
to persuade her not to commit suicide?
That's a new one.
I was trying to distract her,
so I'd have a better chance of saving her.
Is that so?
Or the truth is...
you chased her naked,
and she got so scared
that she fled to the roof?
No.
Do I look like a pervert?
Didn't you look like a pervert
when you pinned her
to the ground half-naked?
I was trying to save her.
When I was trying to carry her down,
I accidentally landed on top of her.
Then why did she call me for help?
She misunderstood.
I can explain it to her again.
Then she'll believe me.
College student.
Perverts always say they aren't.
I told you it wasn't like that.
Poor Kai.
Get up. What time is it?
What time is it?
It's noon.
Hurry up.
We're setting up the stall today.
We have a customer waiting.
Don't you have to make money
to pay for that girl's phone?
Why did that girl
use a Pro phone?
You shouldn't have meddled
in other people's business.
So, what happened to that girl?
Jeff, you finally answered me.
Why have you been
ignoring me and my messages?
You could have told me
your grandpa was sick.
I could have helped, dummy.
I just saw her threads were broken.
I knew she might do something stupid,
so I followed her.
That's not the point.
At least you didn't get sued, right?
Didn't the police think
you were a pervert?
Right.
Getting stuck with a cop who won't listen
is just my bad luck.
But seriously,
was she pretty?
Are we overdoing it
with all these things?
No, it's just right.
Look at how I arranged them here.
The colors are nice, and it looks
professional. It's not bad, right?
[President of the Psychic Club]
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to the Psychic Club.
I'm Chaonan,
president of the Psychic Club.
This is Jiakai,
the darling of the Psychic Club.
Here, we will use psychic methods
to solve your interpersonal problems.
Both people asking questions
need to come in person
or
bring the photos,
and Jiakai
can use his psychic abilities
to see the threads
between you.
Let me briefly explain.
The red thread represents love.
[Red thread—Love]
The green thread represents family.
[Green thread—Family]
The yellow thread represents friendship.
[Yellow thread—Friendship]
The blue thread represents hostility,
and so on.
[Blue thread—Hostility]
Every thread has its meaning.
And the thicker
and more solid the thread is...
Cut.
99% of the people
who come here ask about love.
Excuse me, are you open?
Yes, we are open.
Please sit down.
What's your question?
We want to ask about our exams.
Exams?
Our questions are all here.
[I have a crush on him.]
[But I lied to him that we were here
to ask if we would pass the exam.]
The exam?
Ok, we can read it for you.
How is it?
I don't usually do readings about exams,
but I took a look,
and I think you will
get good results this time.
-Great.
-Thank you.
We'll be leaving now.
-Bye-bye.
We almost closed our first deal.
But you forgot to collect the money.
Excuse me, about the money...
I'd like to ask
about my relationship with this girl.
Oh, okay. Let us take a look.
Hey,
did you do something
that made her unhappy?
How is that possible?
I try to make her happy every day.
Really? What have you
been doing to make her happy?
Look, she said she likes
listening to rap songs,
so I record one for her every day.
Hey girl. You are really cute.
I have a cat at home
that can do backflips.
Do you want to come see my cat?
I've got something even better
to show you.
Something better.
Well, I'd like to know...
This guy is my boyfriend,
and our relationship is pretty good.
-But he's been very cold to me lately.
-Oh, why is that?
Can you help me see what the problem is?
Let us take a look.
Take a look.
The reading takes some time.
It takes some time.
What?
Wait a moment.
I don't know how to say this.
What do you mean? Just say it.
Her boyfriend likes the guy next to him.
It's actually pretty simple.
You just need to cut back on
group outings with him.
Group outings
could affect the connection between you.
So is there still a chance for us
to get back to how we were?
Of course there is.
It just takes a little time.
Great. Thank you.
-I'll put it here.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. Bye-bye.
Good luck.
What's going on?
Her boyfriend has threads on both sides,
so he's into both.
What? You're so vulgar.
But you know,
don't make this gesture.
Checking the mirror again.
I'm telling you,
you're just naturally threadless.
No matter how long you look,
you won't have any threads.
I know.
You know.
You know, yet you still look.
Seeing everyone with so many threads
makes me jealous.
Look at you,
you have a bunch of threads too.
Why am I the only freak
without a single thread?
I've got plenty of threads?
Not there.
On your head.
Whatever, cut the crap.
Do you remember what the Eighth Prince
reminded you of before?
He means
you are different from others
because you carry a divine destiny.
It means
you'll naturally know
when the deity needs you.
A divine destiny is different
from being a freak.
Did you listen to what he said?
I did.
But I still care about it.
That's all that matters.
Are you open?
Am I the first customer today?
Why are you here?
I already paid you
for the phone, didn't I?
I received your money last week.
I also bought a new phone.
Oh, she's that mixed-race jumping girl?
What jumping girl? That sounds awful.
Just call me Yujing.
Yujing,
what brings you here today?
This is a photo
of me and my boyfriend, Jeff.
Take a look for me.
Is he that jerk boyfriend
you mentioned last time?
He hasn't been that bad lately.
I exaggerated it last time.
Cut the crap and give me the money.
It's nothing.
You two only have this one photo together.
You don't have any other photos together?
Are you in a long-distance relationship?
Yeah.
We met on a dating app
and have been dating for five months.
If you've been together for over 3 months,
that's true love, right?
Let me take a look.
Okay.
What's wrong? Are we not a good match?
Not exactly.
You might encounter some ups and downs
or difficulties along the way.
You might need to build
more trust between you.
That way, you'll have a chance
to get through them
and keep moving forward together.
So you mean we are true love?
Yes. You two are true love.
Thanks! I feel confident
about this relationship again.
How much is it?
Three hundred.
Thank you.
I'll come back if I have more questions.
Okay, bye-bye.
Take care. Come back anytime.
Why tell her so much? We've got her money.
Damn.
That guy Danny
is dating a junior
from the Foreign Languages Department.
Tell me.
Why don't Tong, Xuan,
and Yilin from the club
like me?
I'm pretty sure all three
of their threads with you are yellow.
Pure yellow.
I really want to be in a relationship.
I think you should break that bad habit
of falling for everyone you see.
Wait a minute.
I saw a news report...
about Officer Wu Dawei.
The one who called you
a pervert last time.
The police have now obtained
[Live]
a complete list of the cash
taken from the victims,
along with evidence documenting
the temple's scam operation.
We investigate cases based on evidence.
So, in principle, we do not
believe in ghosts, gods,
the Third Eye, or Psychic Abilities.
He's talking about you.
No wonder we can't stand each other.
Do you know how outrageous
that temple priest was?
I just transferred him
to the District Prosecutors Office.
I saw some people trying
to beat him up on the street.
He scammed people out of several million,
so I guess it's understandable
that people wanted to beat him up.
I also heard about a woman
who ran a small restaurant by herself
and worked hard to raise three children.
She withdrew all her savings
and gave it to the temple priest
because she wanted
to pray for a good marriage.
Isn't that pitiful?
I don't think those people need sympathy.
They need to think rationally.
They should take this opportunity
to stop being so superstitious.
Otherwise, sooner or later,
they'll get scammed again.
Dawei,
talking to a cold-blooded
rational person like you
is really boring.
Exactly.
Officer, I want to report a case.
[Psychic]
[Consultations and Finding People]
Why him?
Sit here?
[Psychic]
[Consultations and Finding People]
Sit wherever you like.
How can I help you?
I want to ask about my love life.
You want to ask about your love life?
Is that not okay?
Of course it is.
Yes, it's okay.
I heard you're pretty accurate.
I am, but wait a moment.
What's going on?
He said on TV that he doesn't believe
in ghosts or people with the Third Eye.
And now he's here asking for a reading.
What's wrong with him?
Maybe he's here to challenge me?
Or he just doesn't like me?
Maybe he wants to test my abilities?
No, I think
he totally believes in this stuff.
He's just pretending to be
all rational and scientific.
He doesn't have a red thread at all.
He looks like an idiot.
Just make something up.
He'll believe anything anyway.
Is that okay?
Of course.
Smile.
Done discussing?
Done.
Did you bring a photo of you
and your girlfriend?
Yes.
She is my girlfriend.
But recently she said
she wants to break up.
I'm really worried.
I want to know if we still have a chance
to stay together.
She's your girlfriend?
Yes.
Are you sure?
Why would I ask you that otherwise?
Right, you dummy.
Sorry.
After looking at it, I think
your relationship
with your girlfriend is pretty ordinary.
I suggest you two
go on more dates
and see if you can bring back
the spark.
Yes, spend more time together.
So,
you think we're a suitable couple?
A perfect match. Totally.
Lin Jiakai.
Jiang Chaonan.
You're suspected of being involved
in a fraud scheme.
Please come with me to the police station.
No.
-We didn't scam anyone.
-I don't know anything.
Do you know Zhang Yujing?
-Zhang Yujing?
Yujing?
Yes, Yujing.
You're suspected of helping
a romance scam syndicate
scam Zhang Yujing out of 300,000.
-No.
-300,000? We haven't even...
If you have anything else to explain,
come back to the station with me.
We only charge 300 yuan a time.
Where would we get that kind of money?
I don't have 300,000.
I don't have 300,000 in my account.
How could I?
-Please, you must have misunderstood.
-We really didn't scam her out of 300,000.
It must be a misunderstanding.
Lin Jiakai.
I actually started to think
you were a good guy.
But you teamed up with Jeff
to scam me out of my money.
You really suck!
Who's Jeff? I don't even know him.
How could I have teamed up with him?
Didn't you say last time
that Jeff and I should trust each other
and overcome difficulties together?
I guess I did say that.
Yeah.
The day after you said that,
he said his grandpa's condition
had gotten worse
and wanted to borrow money from me.
So I sent him money
from my mom's account.
And then what?
After getting the money,
he started acting distant.
Now he's vanished into thin air!
How could it be such a coincidence?
Is it just a coincidence?
Combined with the scam
and the fact that you were suspected
of stalking and sexually harassing her
a few weeks ago,
these two incidents suggest
that you may have deliberately
approached her
with a plan in mind.
Officer.
I said it many times last time.
The rooftop incident
was really just a coincidence.
I was trying to save her.
And as for this reading,
Yujing came to us on her own.
We didn't go looking for her.
Exactly.
You...
Then how do you explain this?
Do you work part-time here?
Yeah, yeah.
-I wasn't talking to you.
-Oh, sorry.
Yes, I do. What's wrong?
This is Jeff's account.
[Check in to get free beer. There are
lots of drinks. Good for gatherings.]
Zhang Yujing said
[But make a reservation first,
or you'll wait too long.]
she found out Jeff
had been to your workplace
[Cute staff. 5 stars.]
twice.
Exactly. Look.
And you still say you don't know him.
He just happened to come to eat.
And he always came on Thursdays.
I wasn't even scheduled on Thursdays.
You won't admit it? You're going
to keep covering for him, aren't you?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, no, no, no.
Then I'll sue you!
Then you'll have to pay me back.
President.
No, no, no.
There is no president.
Didn't you say you'd take 70%
and I'd take 30% from the Psychic Club,
-so you'll help me deal with these...
-See? He said that...
-Our Psychic Club tells people's fortunes.
-I confess.
I also said it today.
Look, look.
You are dead meat.
Aren't you going to eat
some pork trotters with vermicelli?
It can ward off bad luck.
I'm not in the mood.
They questioned us
for three hours straight.
They didn't even let me take a shit.
So much for human rights.
I told you that cop was annoying, right?
He was stubborn and wouldn't listen.
During the whole interrogation,
he just kept making up
his own version of what happened.
Good thing
you weren't working when Jeff came.
They couldn't find
any suspicious communication records.
Otherwise, you'd be behind bars.
I'm really unlucky.
By the way.
People are saying we're a scam ring.
What should we do?
Should we keep the Psychic Club going?
I guess we can only
put it on hold for now.
I guess I'll have to pick up more shifts
at my part-time job.
Club Darling, help me out.
Help you with what?
This guy I had a thing with
suddenly stopped talking to me.
I'm not really in a position
to do readings right now.
Please.
Help me one more time.
Take a look at this photo for me.
It's really not convenient
for me right now.
-You might have to find someone else.
-Please.
Please? You're the best.
Fine.
He still likes you.
-I'd say he likes you quite a lot.
-Really?
Try reaching out
to him again after a while.
That's a relief.
Is 300 yuan okay this time?
No need, no need.
Let's just call it a chat this time.
-No need...
-No way.
-No need, really.
-You helped me. I must help you.
Really, no need. Just keep it yourself.
It's alright.
Next time I will...
Why did she give you money?
You're doing readings again?
No.
Did he do a psychic reading for you?
Yeah.
Please leave first.
And thanks for your honesty.
It's not what you think.
Perverted College Student,
do you know you're still a suspect?
That's why I tried
to turn her down just now.
Looks like you're coming back
to the station with me.
I'll let your manager know.
I'll tell the manager myself.
She'll get the wrong idea if you tell her.
Please. Please.
The thread...
Am I seeing this right?
What are you doing?
It really is a thread.
My first thread.
What thread?
How could it be connected to you?
What are you doing?
I can't believe I finally
found my connection.
But... how is this possible?